that one of the bullet casings read,
hey, fascist, catch on it.
One of the other bullet casings right next to that
had Bella Chao written on it.
Now, Bella Chao is a song that is known in Antifa circles
as the international anthem of Antifa.
And all of us around this room that have studied Antifa
were very familiar with these symbols.
And Mr. President, I think the situation is getting worse.
When you look at people like Luigi Maggioni
in his 20s, Thomas Matthew Crooks, of course,
who took a shot at you, sir, the ice shooter in Dallas,
and now this Tyler Robinson,
we're starting to see a pattern
of more and more murderous violence.
And this same violence is not just random.
It is targeted assassinations, which are getting worse.
And every single one of us in this room.